( crow cawing )
( bird chirping )
THE PEACH OPEN MOVIE PROJECT
PRESENTS
BIG BUCK BUNNY
( snoring )
( yawning )
( peaceful music playing )
( chomps )
( footsteps running )
( leaves rustling )
( sneaky music playing )
( squirrel chirps )
( squirrels laughing )
( banging )
- ( action music playing )
- ( banging continues )
( sad music playing )
( action music playing )
( epic music playing )
( joyful music playing )
( epic music continues )
- ( branch cracking )
- ( squirrels chirping )
( screams )
- ( exclaims )
- ( rumbling )
( screams )
( branches cracking )
( leaves snapping )
( screams )
( squirrel screaming )
( heroic music playing )
( epic closing music playing )
( epic closing music continues )
- ( eagles cawing, birds chirping )
- ( wind rustling )